I sent my father to the dairy to get some supplies.  Dad was having a
chat with his brother, and I told him how much I had
talked to him about getting him to come quickly from upstairs.
Meanwhile, my brother kept
chatting with his grandfather, saying that he would come in a moment.
How stupid is that?  I was
having tea here and they also came, didn't they? They
brought their brother. Even my sister
thinks it's so much fun to play with Grandpa. And the
son brought all the things he said, "Brought everything,
sir." He went inside, saying, "How much has it been?"  Brother, if you
eat tea, you don't eat. Hey, are these
two brothers going to sit together for a while after they get together
and play the game? Yeah.